const trivia = [
    {
        question: "What were the names of Clark Kent's parents?",
        answer: "johnathan and martha kent"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Flash saved the multiverse in Crisis on Infinite Earths?",
        answer: "Barry Allen" 
    },
    {
        question: 'Finish this quote "In brightest day..."',
        answer: "in blackest night" 
    }, 
    {
        question: "In what country did the Red Son land in?",
        answer: "Soviet Union"
    },
    {
        question: "Name the 5 Robins in chronological order",
        answer: "Dick Grayson, Jason Todd, Tim Drake, Stephanie Brown, Damian Wayne"
    },
    {
        question: 'Finish this quote "You\'ve got heart kid, where are you from?"',
        answer: "Queens"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Virgil Hawkins alter ego?",
        answer: "Static Shock"
    },
    {
        question: "What Avenger said...'I can do this all day'",
        answer: "Captain America"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Wally West's alter ego?",
        answer: "Kid Flash"
    },
    {
        question: "From where does Ras Al Ghul get his immorality?",
        answer: "Lazarus Pit"
    },
    {
        question: "Who said... 'There is a difference between you and me. We both looked into the abyss, but when it looked back, you blinked'",
        answer: "Batman"
    },
    {
        question: "Who said... 'You stay, I go, no following'",
        answer: "Iron Giant"
    },
    {
        question: "This character made his first apperance in Infinte Crisis in issue #3 under the alias Blue Beeatle",
        answer: "Jamie Ryes"
    },
    {
        question: "In what city, State is Clark Kent from?",
        answer: "Smallvile, Kansas"
    },
    {
        question: "This villian's origin story is seen  in Detective comics 'The Man behind the Red Hood'",
        answer: "Joke"
    }
]

